{
  "EI": [
    {
      "id": 5,
      "prompt": "Deep down, are you more angry or resentful?",
      "left": "angry",
      "right": "resentful",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0.21,
        "E": 0,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.02,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0,
        "J": 0.04,
        "P": 0
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: talks over a decision with other people or makes it alone?",
      "left": "talks over a decision with other people",
      "right": "makes it alone",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0.89,
        "E": 0,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.48,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.84,
        "J": 0.04,
        "P": 0
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 11,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: learns before doing or learns while doing?",
      "left": "learns before doing",
      "right": "learns while doing",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0,
        "E": 0.72,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.03,
        "F": 0.26,
        "T": 0,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.65
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 12,
      "prompt": "In everyday life, are you more careful or extreme?",
      "left": "careful",
      "right": "extreme",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0,
        "E": 0.73,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.18,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.02,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.65
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 14,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: learns by doing or learns by watching?",
      "left": "learns by doing",
      "right": "learns by watching",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0.34,
        "E": 0,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.24,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.13,
        "J": 0.1,
        "P": 0
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 17,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: often thinks about what they should have done differently or does not second guess?",
      "left": "often thinks about what they should have done differently",
      "right": "does not second guess",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0,
        "E": 0.46,
        "S": 0.03,
        "N": 0,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.09,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.09
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 18,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: likes small talk or hates small talk?",
      "left": "likes small talk",
      "right": "hates small talk",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0.98,
        "E": 0,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.25,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.28,
        "J": 0.15,
        "P": 0
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 25,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: wants to be treated right or just doesn't want to be treated wrong?",
      "left": "wants to be treated right",
      "right": "just doesn't want to be treated wrong",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0.3,
        "E": 0,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.28,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.25
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 27,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: wants a destiny or afraid of fate?",
      "left": "wants a destiny",
      "right": "afraid of fate",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0.2,
        "E": 0,
        "S": 0.13,
        "N": 0,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.19,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.06
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 30,
      "prompt": "Are you more confident or unsure?",
      "left": "confident",
      "right": "unsure",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0.92,
        "E": 0,
        "S": 0.1,
        "N": 0,
        "F": 0.4,
        "T": 0,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.33
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 33,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: manipulates things behind the scenes or leads from the front?",
      "left": "manipulates things behind the scenes",
      "right": "leads from the front",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0,
        "E": 1.12,
        "S": 0.11,
        "N": 0,
        "F": 0.13,
        "T": 0,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.04
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 34,
      "prompt": "Deep down, are you more trusting or paranoid?",
      "left": "trusting",
      "right": "paranoid",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0.6,
        "E": 0,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.12,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.43,
        "J": 0.07,
        "P": 0
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 39,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: feels unlucky or feels very lucky?",
      "left": "feels unlucky",
      "right": "feels very lucky",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0,
        "E": 0.68,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.05,
        "F": 0.12,
        "T": 0,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.05
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 42,
      "prompt": "Day to day, are you more cautious or bold?",
      "left": "cautious",
      "right": "bold",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0,
        "E": 1.04,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.23,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.07,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.36
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 44,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: caffeine (or other stimulant) gives a major boost or hardly notices the effects?",
      "left": "caffeine (or other stimulant) gives a major boost",
      "right": "hardly notices the effects",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0.31,
        "E": 0,
        "S": 0.13,
        "N": 0,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.28,
        "J": 0.01,
        "P": 0
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 45,
      "prompt": "Are you more somber or enthusiastic?",
      "left": "somber",
      "right": "enthusiastic",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0,
        "E": 1.33,
        "S": 0.02,
        "N": 0,
        "F": 0.54,
        "T": 0,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.31
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 46,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: wants loyal friends or wants fun friends?",
      "left": "wants loyal friends",
      "right": "wants fun friends",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0,
        "E": 0.5,
        "S": 0.07,
        "N": 0,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.06,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.43
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 47,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: no one knows what they are talking about or some people know what they are talking about?",
      "left": "no one knows what they are talking about",
      "right": "some people know what they are talking about",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0,
        "E": 0.36,
        "S": 0.11,
        "N": 0,
        "F": 0.32,
        "T": 0,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.02
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 49,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: like to listen to stories or likes to tell stories?",
      "left": "like to listen to stories",
      "right": "likes to tell stories",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0,
        "E": 0.94,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.1,
        "F": 0.06,
        "T": 0,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.15
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 59,
      "prompt": "When people describe you, are you more abstains or indulges?",
      "left": "abstains",
      "right": "indulges",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0,
        "E": 0.57,
        "S": 0.09,
        "N": 0,
        "F": 0.27,
        "T": 0,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.39
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 61,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: fears sharing secrets or enjoys sharing secrets?",
      "left": "fears sharing secrets",
      "right": "enjoys sharing secrets",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0,
        "E": 0.97,
        "S": 0.1,
        "N": 0,
        "F": 0.5,
        "T": 0,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.3
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 63,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: careful or lives dangerously?",
      "left": "careful",
      "right": "lives dangerously",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0,
        "E": 0.76,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.27,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.01,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.71
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 64,
      "prompt": "Day to day, are you more careful or spontaneous?",
      "left": "careful",
      "right": "spontaneous",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0,
        "E": 0.99,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.11,
        "F": 0.25,
        "T": 0,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.85
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 66,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: reads books or watches movies?",
      "left": "reads books",
      "right": "watches movies",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0,
        "E": 0.37,
        "S": 0.25,
        "N": 0,
        "F": 0.27,
        "T": 0,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.19
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 68,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: likes being drunk or feels uncomfortable when drunk?",
      "left": "likes being drunk",
      "right": "feels uncomfortable when drunk",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0.61,
        "E": 0,
        "S": 0.05,
        "N": 0,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.15,
        "J": 0.52,
        "P": 0
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 69,
      "prompt": "Are you more energetic or mellow?",
      "left": "energetic",
      "right": "mellow",
      "weights": {
        "I": 1.24,
        "E": 0,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.11,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.15,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.05
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 74,
      "prompt": "In everyday life, are you more friendly or distant?",
      "left": "friendly",
      "right": "distant",
      "weights": {
        "I": 1.26,
        "E": 0,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.27,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.74,
        "J": 0.13,
        "P": 0
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 77,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: thinks about things from the top down or reasons from the bottom up?",
      "left": "thinks about things from the top down",
      "right": "reasons from the bottom up",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0.24,
        "E": 0,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.14,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.05,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.11
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 79,
      "prompt": "When people describe you, are you more well-rounded or deep?",
      "left": "well-rounded",
      "right": "deep",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0.64,
        "E": 0,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.42,
        "F": 0.14,
        "T": 0,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.1
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 81,
      "prompt": "Day to day, are you more enthusiastic or deliberate?",
      "left": "enthusiastic",
      "right": "deliberate",
      "weights": {
        "I": 1.17,
        "E": 0,
        "S": 0.04,
        "N": 0,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.8,
        "J": 0.53,
        "P": 0
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 83,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: has not changed much or very different than before?",
      "left": "has not changed much",
      "right": "very different than before",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0,
        "E": 0.37,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.16,
        "F": 0.13,
        "T": 0,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.29
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 84,
      "prompt": "Are you more tense or relaxed?",
      "left": "tense",
      "right": "relaxed",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0,
        "E": 0.6,
        "S": 0.1,
        "N": 0,
        "F": 0.15,
        "T": 0,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.37
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 88,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: liked school or hated school?",
      "left": "liked school",
      "right": "hated school",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0.38,
        "E": 0,
        "S": 0.06,
        "N": 0,
        "F": 0.05,
        "T": 0,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.35
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 89,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: comes up with ideas and convinces other people of them or critically evaluates the ideas of others?",
      "left": "comes up with ideas and convinces other people of them",
      "right": "critically evaluates the ideas of others",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0.66,
        "E": 0,
        "S": 0.26,
        "N": 0,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.26,
        "J": 0.26,
        "P": 0
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 95,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: listens more or talks more?",
      "left": "listens more",
      "right": "talks more",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0,
        "E": 1.37,
        "S": 0.06,
        "N": 0,
        "F": 0.09,
        "T": 0,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.23
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 97,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: prefers to be first mate or prefers to be captain?",
      "left": "prefers to be first mate",
      "right": "prefers to be captain",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0,
        "E": 0.93,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.18,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.36,
        "J": 0.11,
        "P": 0
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 98,
      "prompt": "When people describe you, are you more flowing or twitching?",
      "left": "flowing",
      "right": "twitching",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0.24,
        "E": 0,
        "S": 0.06,
        "N": 0,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.13,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.04
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 102,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: has deep interests or has many interests?",
      "left": "has deep interests",
      "right": "has many interests",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0,
        "E": 0.72,
        "S": 0.15,
        "N": 0,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.05,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.32
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 105,
      "prompt": "Deep down, are you more people-oriented or task-oriented?",
      "left": "people-oriented",
      "right": "task-oriented",
      "weights": {
        "I": 1.23,
        "E": 0,
        "S": 0.07,
        "N": 0,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 1.1,
        "J": 0.57,
        "P": 0
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 107,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: tells others about their plans or tells others about what they have done?",
      "left": "tells others about their plans",
      "right": "tells others about what they have done",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0.22,
        "E": 0,
        "S": 0.1,
        "N": 0,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.17,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.08
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 108,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: keep room door closed or leaves door open?",
      "left": "keep room door closed",
      "right": "leaves door open",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0,
        "E": 0.83,
        "S": 0.09,
        "N": 0,
        "F": 0.17,
        "T": 0,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.08
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 110,
      "prompt": "In everyday life, are you more eager or reluctant?",
      "left": "eager",
      "right": "reluctant",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0.86,
        "E": 0,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.01,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.33,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.08
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 112,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: criticizes themselves or accepts themselves?",
      "left": "criticizes themselves",
      "right": "accepts themselves",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0,
        "E": 0.48,
        "S": 0.02,
        "N": 0,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.1,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.1
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 114,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: quick thinker or deep thinker?",
      "left": "quick thinker",
      "right": "deep thinker",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0.79,
        "E": 0,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.37,
        "F": 0.18,
        "T": 0,
        "J": 0.03,
        "P": 0
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 117,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: notices a person' or s physical appearance first?",
      "left": "notices a person'",
      "right": "s physical appearance first",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0,
        "E": 0.21,
        "S": 0.21,
        "N": 0,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.14,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.09
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 119,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: hates the dentist or does not mind the dentist?",
      "left": "hates the dentist",
      "right": "does not mind the dentist",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0,
        "E": 0.19,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.02,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.11,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.03
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 123,
      "prompt": "Day to day, are you more timid or offensive?",
      "left": "timid",
      "right": "offensive",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0,
        "E": 0.98,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.1,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.48,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.04
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 126,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: works best alone or works best in groups?",
      "left": "works best alone",
      "right": "works best in groups",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0,
        "E": 1.19,
        "S": 0.09,
        "N": 0,
        "F": 0.33,
        "T": 0,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.21
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 132,
      "prompt": "In everyday life, are you more hopeful or fearful?",
      "left": "hopeful",
      "right": "fearful",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0.68,
        "E": 0,
        "S": 0.11,
        "N": 0,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.09,
        "J": 0.01,
        "P": 0
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 135,
      "prompt": "When people describe you, are you more comfortable or troubled?",
      "left": "comfortable",
      "right": "troubled",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0.71,
        "E": 0,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.26,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.08,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.11
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 138,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: has to be lost for a long time before they ask for help or will stop and ask for directions right away?",
      "left": "has to be lost for a long time before they ask for help",
      "right": "will stop and ask for directions right away",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0,
        "E": 0.69,
        "S": 0.08,
        "N": 0,
        "F": 0.19,
        "T": 0,
        "J": 0.25,
        "P": 0
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 139,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: feels very lucky or feels unlucky?",
      "left": "feels very lucky",
      "right": "feels unlucky",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0.69,
        "E": 0,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.04,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.04,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.04
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 142,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: jokes about things or jokes about people?",
      "left": "jokes about things",
      "right": "jokes about people",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0,
        "E": 0.39,
        "S": 0.07,
        "N": 0,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.23,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.06
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 144,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: gets broken up with or does the breaking up?",
      "left": "gets broken up with",
      "right": "does the breaking up",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0,
        "E": 0.37,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.1,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.33,
        "J": 0.2,
        "P": 0
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 145,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: likes change or resists change?",
      "left": "likes change",
      "right": "resists change",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0.53,
        "E": 0,
        "S": 0.38,
        "N": 0,
        "F": 0.05,
        "T": 0,
        "J": 0.37,
        "P": 0
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 146,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: eats quickly or savours the flavour?",
      "left": "eats quickly",
      "right": "savours the flavour",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0.22,
        "E": 0,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.04,
        "F": 0.13,
        "T": 0,
        "J": 0.09,
        "P": 0
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 147,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: finds the world interesting or finds the world boring?",
      "left": "finds the world interesting",
      "right": "finds the world boring",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0.25,
        "E": 0,
        "S": 0.1,
        "N": 0,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.17,
        "J": 0.07,
        "P": 0
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 149,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: remembers everything they did on their birthday before last or remembers not so much?",
      "left": "remembers everything they did on their birthday before last",
      "right": "remembers not so much",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0.39,
        "E": 0,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.29,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.18,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.19
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 154,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: gets worn out by parties or gets fired up by parties?",
      "left": "gets worn out by parties",
      "right": "gets fired up by parties",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0,
        "E": 1.77,
        "S": 0.2,
        "N": 0,
        "F": 0.21,
        "T": 0,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.35
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 159,
      "prompt": "Day to day, are you more cheerful or gloomy?",
      "left": "cheerful",
      "right": "gloomy",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0.91,
        "E": 0,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.18,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.44,
        "J": 0.04,
        "P": 0
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 168,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: eats slowly or eats rapidly?",
      "left": "eats slowly",
      "right": "eats rapidly",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0,
        "E": 0.22,
        "S": 0.02,
        "N": 0,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.03,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.03
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 172,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: finds it difficult to yell very loudly or yelling to others when they are far away comes naturally?",
      "left": "finds it difficult to yell very loudly",
      "right": "yelling to others when they are far away comes naturally",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0,
        "E": 1.4,
        "S": 0.11,
        "N": 0,
        "F": 0.05,
        "T": 0,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.18
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 174,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: wants a big house or wants a cozy house?",
      "left": "wants a big house",
      "right": "wants a cozy house",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0.52,
        "E": 0,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.07,
        "F": 0.33,
        "T": 0,
        "J": 0.02,
        "P": 0
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 178,
      "prompt": "In everyday life, are you more serious or silly?",
      "left": "serious",
      "right": "silly",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0,
        "E": 0.64,
        "S": 0.03,
        "N": 0,
        "F": 0.51,
        "T": 0,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.58
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 183,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: sees the glass as glass half full or sees it as half empty?",
      "left": "sees the glass as glass half full",
      "right": "sees it as half empty",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0.71,
        "E": 0,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.03,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.35,
        "J": 0.05,
        "P": 0
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 184,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: needs time alone or bored by time alone?",
      "left": "needs time alone",
      "right": "bored by time alone",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0,
        "E": 1.44,
        "S": 0.18,
        "N": 0,
        "F": 0.18,
        "T": 0,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.22
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 188,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: likes to perform in front of other people or avoids public speaking?",
      "left": "likes to perform in front of other people",
      "right": "avoids public speaking",
      "weights": {
        "I": 1.41,
        "E": 0,
        "S": 0.1,
        "N": 0,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.04,
        "J": 0.05,
        "P": 0
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 191,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: takes stuff to mellow out or takes stuff to amp up?",
      "left": "takes stuff to mellow out",
      "right": "takes stuff to amp up",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0,
        "E": 0.28,
        "S": 0.25,
        "N": 0,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.07,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.03
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 192,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: stays at home or goes out on the town?",
      "left": "stays at home",
      "right": "goes out on the town",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0,
        "E": 1.43,
        "S": 0.05,
        "N": 0,
        "F": 0.18,
        "T": 0,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.26
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 193,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: likes civilization or wants to get back to nature?",
      "left": "likes civilization",
      "right": "wants to get back to nature",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0.36,
        "E": 0,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.25,
        "F": 0.3,
        "T": 0,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.21
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 195,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: likes to drive fast or likes to keep it under control?",
      "left": "likes to drive fast",
      "right": "likes to keep it under control",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0.64,
        "E": 0,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.11,
        "F": 0.07,
        "T": 0,
        "J": 0.47,
        "P": 0
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 197,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: frequently embarrassed or shameless?",
      "left": "frequently embarrassed",
      "right": "shameless",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0,
        "E": 0.93,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.1,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.37,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.13
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 198,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: needs silence to sleep or can sleep through anything?",
      "left": "needs silence to sleep",
      "right": "can sleep through anything",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0,
        "E": 0.58,
        "S": 0.1,
        "N": 0,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.06,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.23
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 199,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: shows anger or hides anger?",
      "left": "shows anger",
      "right": "hides anger",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0.64,
        "E": 0,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.11,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.22,
        "J": 0.05,
        "P": 0
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 202,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: likes team sports or likes individual sports?",
      "left": "likes team sports",
      "right": "likes individual sports",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0.8,
        "E": 0,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.37,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.31,
        "J": 0.09,
        "P": 0
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 204,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: bounces around the room or remains calm?",
      "left": "bounces around the room",
      "right": "remains calm",
      "weights": {
        "I": 1.31,
        "E": 0,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.03,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.44,
        "J": 0.5,
        "P": 0
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 209,
      "prompt": "Are you more brave or careful?",
      "left": "brave",
      "right": "careful",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0.77,
        "E": 0,
        "S": 0.23,
        "N": 0,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.02,
        "J": 0.15,
        "P": 0
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 210,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: hates people who show off or maybe a little impressed by people who show off?",
      "left": "hates people who show off",
      "right": "maybe a little impressed by people who show off",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0,
        "E": 0.51,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.02,
        "F": 0.24,
        "T": 0,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.27
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 216,
      "prompt": "In everyday life, are you more passive or aggressive?",
      "left": "passive",
      "right": "aggressive",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0,
        "E": 0.86,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.04,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.37,
        "J": 0.13,
        "P": 0
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 218,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: makes repairs or buys new?",
      "left": "makes repairs",
      "right": "buys new",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0,
        "E": 0.23,
        "S": 0.11,
        "N": 0,
        "F": 0.12,
        "T": 0,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.13
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 220,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: reacts deliberately or reacts instantly?",
      "left": "reacts deliberately",
      "right": "reacts instantly",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0,
        "E": 0.67,
        "S": 0.26,
        "N": 0,
        "F": 0.36,
        "T": 0,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.46
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 221,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: has many interests or has deep interests?",
      "left": "has many interests",
      "right": "has deep interests",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0.82,
        "E": 0,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.11,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.08,
        "J": 0.25,
        "P": 0
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 226,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: likes spring or likes fall?",
      "left": "likes spring",
      "right": "likes fall",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0.48,
        "E": 0,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.39,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.24,
        "J": 0.11,
        "P": 0
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 229,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: poor sense of smell or good sense of smell?",
      "left": "poor sense of smell",
      "right": "good sense of smell",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0,
        "E": 0.17,
        "S": 0.06,
        "N": 0,
        "F": 0.12,
        "T": 0,
        "J": 0.02,
        "P": 0
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 232,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: bonds over shared interests or bonds through shared experience?",
      "left": "bonds over shared interests",
      "right": "bonds through shared experience",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0,
        "E": 0.37,
        "S": 0.14,
        "N": 0,
        "F": 0.26,
        "T": 0,
        "J": 0.04,
        "P": 0
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 238,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: hates conflict or makes trouble?",
      "left": "hates conflict",
      "right": "makes trouble",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0,
        "E": 0.64,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.14,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.52,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.23
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 241,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: prefers to be captain or rather be first mate?",
      "left": "prefers to be captain",
      "right": "rather be first mate",
      "weights": {
        "I": 1.02,
        "E": 0,
        "S": 0.21,
        "N": 0,
        "F": 0.39,
        "T": 0,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.19
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 242,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: does not vary diet or tries new foods?",
      "left": "does not vary diet",
      "right": "tries new foods",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0,
        "E": 0.59,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.26,
        "F": 0.15,
        "T": 0,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.21
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 247,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: wants deep friendships or wants many friendships?",
      "left": "wants deep friendships",
      "right": "wants many friendships",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0,
        "E": 0.77,
        "S": 0.11,
        "N": 0,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.08,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.15
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 250,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: prefer to run a small business or prefer to run a large corporation?",
      "left": "prefer to run a small business",
      "right": "prefer to run a large corporation",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0,
        "E": 0.64,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.07,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.63,
        "J": 0.07,
        "P": 0
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 255,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: likes to tell stories or like to listen to stories?",
      "left": "likes to tell stories",
      "right": "like to listen to stories",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0.96,
        "E": 0,
        "S": 0.05,
        "N": 0,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.14,
        "J": 0.13,
        "P": 0
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 256,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: always looking to taste something new or could eat the same thing every day?",
      "left": "always looking to taste something new",
      "right": "could eat the same thing every day",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0.51,
        "E": 0,
        "S": 0.28,
        "N": 0,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.03,
        "J": 0.33,
        "P": 0
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 257,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: likes sports or bored by sports?",
      "left": "likes sports",
      "right": "bored by sports",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0.7,
        "E": 0,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.39,
        "F": 0.03,
        "T": 0,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.1
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 258,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: hates being photographed or loves it?",
      "left": "hates being photographed",
      "right": "loves it",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0,
        "E": 1.06,
        "S": 0.25,
        "N": 0,
        "F": 0.44,
        "T": 0,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.21
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 261,
      "prompt": "Are you more open or guarded?",
      "left": "open",
      "right": "guarded",
      "weights": {
        "I": 1.41,
        "E": 0,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.04,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.67,
        "J": 0.33,
        "P": 0
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 263,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: leads from the front or manipulates things behind the scenes?",
      "left": "leads from the front",
      "right": "manipulates things behind the scenes",
      "weights": {
        "I": 1.16,
        "E": 0,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.27,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.29,
        "J": 0.09,
        "P": 0
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 266,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: reads the instructions first or jumps right into it?",
      "left": "reads the instructions first",
      "right": "jumps right into it",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0,
        "E": 0.57,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.03,
        "F": 0.18,
        "T": 0,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.54
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 268,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: feels most content at the start of the day or feels most content at the end of the day?",
      "left": "feels most content at the start of the day",
      "right": "feels most content at the end of the day",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0.23,
        "E": 0,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.04,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.17,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.11
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 269,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: would enjoy being stranded on an island or would want to be rescued as quickly as possible?",
      "left": "would enjoy being stranded on an island",
      "right": "would want to be rescued as quickly as possible",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0,
        "E": 0.81,
        "S": 0.46,
        "N": 0,
        "F": 0.3,
        "T": 0,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.04
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 270,
      "prompt": "When people describe you, are you more reflective or active?",
      "left": "reflective",
      "right": "active",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0,
        "E": 1,
        "S": 0.4,
        "N": 0,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.09,
        "J": 0.03,
        "P": 0
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 273,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: still in contact with first friends or loses touch with old friends?",
      "left": "still in contact with first friends",
      "right": "loses touch with old friends",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0.57,
        "E": 0,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.35,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.3,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.22
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 276,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: embarrassed by the things they daydream about or proud of the things they daydream about?",
      "left": "embarrassed by the things they daydream about",
      "right": "proud of the things they daydream about",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0,
        "E": 0.46,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.31,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.1,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.19
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 278,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: has difficulty explaining their ideas or confident explaining their ideas?",
      "left": "has difficulty explaining their ideas",
      "right": "confident explaining their ideas",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0,
        "E": 1.02,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.26,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.31,
        "J": 0.13,
        "P": 0
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 279,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: focuses on one thing at a time or multitasks?",
      "left": "focuses on one thing at a time",
      "right": "multitasks",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0,
        "E": 0.47,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.14,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.04,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.33
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 282,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: obsessed with travelling or no need to see the world?",
      "left": "obsessed with travelling",
      "right": "no need to see the world",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0.35,
        "E": 0,
        "S": 0.08,
        "N": 0,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.22,
        "J": 0.23,
        "P": 0
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 284,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: no need to see the world or obsessed with travelling?",
      "left": "no need to see the world",
      "right": "obsessed with travelling",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0,
        "E": 0.47,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.15,
        "F": 0.25,
        "T": 0,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.33
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 288,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: prefer to be wealthy or prefer to be famous?",
      "left": "prefer to be wealthy",
      "right": "prefer to be famous",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0,
        "E": 0.41,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.15,
        "F": 0.36,
        "T": 0,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.22
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 290,
      "prompt": "Are you more mellow or energetic?",
      "left": "mellow",
      "right": "energetic",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0,
        "E": 1.37,
        "S": 0.05,
        "N": 0,
        "F": 0.12,
        "T": 0,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.14
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 294,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: happy at home or obsessed with travelling?",
      "left": "happy at home",
      "right": "obsessed with travelling",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0,
        "E": 0.78,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.09,
        "F": 0.17,
        "T": 0,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.32
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 296,
      "prompt": "In everyday life, are you more okay or perfect?",
      "left": "okay",
      "right": "perfect",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0,
        "E": 0.46,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.14,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.41,
        "J": 0.28,
        "P": 0
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 298,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: saves it or uses it?",
      "left": "saves it",
      "right": "uses it",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0,
        "E": 0.39,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.05,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.18,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.29
      }
    }
  ],
  "SN": [
    {
      "id": 21,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: interested in realities or interested in possibilities?",
      "left": "interested in realities",
      "right": "interested in possibilities",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0,
        "E": 0.14,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.75,
        "F": 0.36,
        "T": 0,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.42
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 23,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: focused on the present or focused on the future?",
      "left": "focused on the present",
      "right": "focused on the future",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0.04,
        "E": 0,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.72,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.1,
        "J": 0.23,
        "P": 0
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 24,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: focuses on the big picture or takes care of the little details?",
      "left": "focuses on the big picture",
      "right": "takes care of the little details",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0.3,
        "E": 0,
        "S": 0.61,
        "N": 0,
        "F": 0.1,
        "T": 0,
        "J": 0.34,
        "P": 0
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 32,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: likes to know \\\"who?\\\", \\\"what?\\\", \\\"when?\\\" or likes to know \\\"why?\\\"?",
      "left": "likes to know \\\"who?\\\", \\\"what?\\\", \\\"when?\\\"",
      "right": "likes to know \\\"why?\\\"",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0.18,
        "E": 0,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.73,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.04,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.19
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 50,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: adapts to the world or wants the world to adapt to them?",
      "left": "adapts to the world",
      "right": "wants the world to adapt to them",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0.23,
        "E": 0,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.33,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.26,
        "J": 0.05,
        "P": 0
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 53,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: will say \\\"these are the things I have made\\\" or will say \\\"these are the things I have designed\\\"?",
      "left": "will say \\\"these are the things I have made\\\"",
      "right": "will say \\\"these are the things I have designed\\\"",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0.05,
        "E": 0,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.63,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.39,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.08
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 54,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: good with names or bad with names?",
      "left": "good with names",
      "right": "bad with names",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0.23,
        "E": 0,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.25,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.24,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.14
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 62,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: wants to impress authority or rebels against authority?",
      "left": "wants to impress authority",
      "right": "rebels against authority",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0.1,
        "E": 0,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.56,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.32,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.53
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 67,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: when describing an event, will tell people what happened or when describing an event, will tell people what it meant?",
      "left": "when describing an event, will tell people what happened",
      "right": "when describing an event, will tell people what it meant",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0.03,
        "E": 0,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.74,
        "F": 0.26,
        "T": 0,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.15
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 76,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: fits in or stands out?",
      "left": "fits in",
      "right": "stands out",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0.04,
        "E": 0,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.48,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.14,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.18
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 78,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: would hate to be called weird or does not want to be thought of as normal?",
      "left": "would hate to be called weird",
      "right": "does not want to be thought of as normal",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0.1,
        "E": 0,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.36,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.12,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.31
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 80,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: wants a normal lifespan or wants to live forever?",
      "left": "wants a normal lifespan",
      "right": "wants to live forever",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0,
        "E": 0.34,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.57,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.28,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.12
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 82,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: tries to be different or tries to be normal?",
      "left": "tries to be different",
      "right": "tries to be normal",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0.18,
        "E": 0,
        "S": 0.43,
        "N": 0,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0,
        "J": 0.23,
        "P": 0
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 104,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: accepts things as they are or unsatisfied with the ways things are?",
      "left": "accepts things as they are",
      "right": "unsatisfied with the ways things are",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0.06,
        "E": 0,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.55,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.15,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 111,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: respects the letter of the law or follows the spirit of the law?",
      "left": "respects the letter of the law",
      "right": "follows the spirit of the law",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0,
        "E": 0.06,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.51,
        "F": 0.27,
        "T": 0,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.5
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 118,
      "prompt": "When people describe you, are you more complicated or uncomplicated?",
      "left": "complicated",
      "right": "uncomplicated",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0,
        "E": 0.27,
        "S": 0.41,
        "N": 0,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.06,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.13
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 120,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: wants the big picture or wants the details?",
      "left": "wants the big picture",
      "right": "wants the details",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0.28,
        "E": 0,
        "S": 0.63,
        "N": 0,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.03,
        "J": 0.18,
        "P": 0
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 127,
      "prompt": "Are you more relaxes or daydreams?",
      "left": "relaxes",
      "right": "daydreams",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0.26,
        "E": 0,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.48,
        "F": 0.22,
        "T": 0,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.34
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 136,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: likes pop music or hates pop music?",
      "left": "likes pop music",
      "right": "hates pop music",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0.3,
        "E": 0,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.44,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.44,
        "J": 0.06,
        "P": 0
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 148,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: likes popular music or likes music that is not well known?",
      "left": "likes popular music",
      "right": "likes music that is not well known",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0.42,
        "E": 0,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.43,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.21,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.24
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 153,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: judges a painting on how realistic it is or judges a painting by deeper criteria?",
      "left": "judges a painting on how realistic it is",
      "right": "judges a painting by deeper criteria",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0.02,
        "E": 0,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.74,
        "F": 0.51,
        "T": 0,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.38
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 157,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: will say \\\"these are the things I have made\\\" or will say \\\"these are the things I have designed\\\"?",
      "left": "will say \\\"these are the things I have made\\\"",
      "right": "will say \\\"these are the things I have designed\\\"",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0.06,
        "E": 0,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.46,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.43,
        "J": 0.11,
        "P": 0
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 160,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: prefers the old ways or tries new ways?",
      "left": "prefers the old ways",
      "right": "tries new ways",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0,
        "E": 0.44,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.55,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.15,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.33
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 161,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: wants aliens to exist or hopes that they do not?",
      "left": "wants aliens to exist",
      "right": "hopes that they do not",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0,
        "E": 0.18,
        "S": 0.43,
        "N": 0,
        "F": 0.13,
        "T": 0,
        "J": 0.26,
        "P": 0
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 185,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: wants the details or wants the big picture?",
      "left": "wants the details",
      "right": "wants the big picture",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0,
        "E": 0.32,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.57,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.05,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.25
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 190,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: wants to be normal or wants to be different?",
      "left": "wants to be normal",
      "right": "wants to be different",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0,
        "E": 0.24,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.51,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.01,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.39
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 201,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: remembers dreams or does not?",
      "left": "remembers dreams",
      "right": "does not",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0.08,
        "E": 0,
        "S": 0.3,
        "N": 0,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.28,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.03
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 205,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: likes stories with lots of action or likes stories with lots of twists?",
      "left": "likes stories with lots of action",
      "right": "likes stories with lots of twists",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0.26,
        "E": 0,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.51,
        "F": 0.03,
        "T": 0,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.04
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 211,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: enjoys mental competition or enjoys physical competition?",
      "left": "enjoys mental competition",
      "right": "enjoys physical competition",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0,
        "E": 0.42,
        "S": 0.47,
        "N": 0,
        "F": 0.18,
        "T": 0,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.07
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 219,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: has an average taste in music or has superior taste in music?",
      "left": "has an average taste in music",
      "right": "has superior taste in music",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0,
        "E": 0.02,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.21,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.01,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.14
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 222,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: prefer to take multiple choice test or prefer essay answers?",
      "left": "prefer to take multiple choice test",
      "right": "prefer essay answers",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0,
        "E": 0.16,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.47,
        "F": 0.08,
        "T": 0,
        "J": 0.01,
        "P": 0
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 233,
      "prompt": "Deep down, are you more empirical or theoretical?",
      "left": "empirical",
      "right": "theoretical",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0.16,
        "E": 0,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.71,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.11,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.22
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 234,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: envious of what other people have or envious of what other people are?",
      "left": "envious of what other people have",
      "right": "envious of what other people are",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0.12,
        "E": 0,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.26,
        "F": 0.14,
        "T": 0,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.1
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 240,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: must be special or content to be normal?",
      "left": "must be special",
      "right": "content to be normal",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0.32,
        "E": 0,
        "S": 0.46,
        "N": 0,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.14,
        "J": 0.27,
        "P": 0
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 253,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: starts over when they fail or tries something new when they fail?",
      "left": "starts over when they fail",
      "right": "tries something new when they fail",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0,
        "E": 0.3,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.36,
        "F": 0.02,
        "T": 0,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.31
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 262,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: tries a sensible solution or tries a clever solution?",
      "left": "tries a sensible solution",
      "right": "tries a clever solution",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0,
        "E": 0.32,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.63,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.34,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.36
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 264,
      "prompt": "Deep down, are you more normal or alternative?",
      "left": "normal",
      "right": "alternative",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0.08,
        "E": 0,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.61,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.02,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.36
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 293,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: likes music or likes the visual arts?",
      "left": "likes music",
      "right": "likes the visual arts",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0.01,
        "E": 0,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.24,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.06,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.11
      }
    }
  ],
  "TF": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "prompt": "Do you get more energized by fast-paced action or drawn into emotional drama?",
      "left": "gets energized by fast-paced action",
      "right": "gets drawn into emotional drama",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0.14,
        "E": 0,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.18,
        "F": 0.49,
        "T": 0,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.21
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "prompt": "Are you more realistic or imaginative?",
      "left": "realistic",
      "right": "imaginative",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0,
        "E": 0.12,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.63,
        "F": 0.71,
        "T": 0,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.71
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: criticism leads to feelings of guilt or criticism leads to feelings of anger?",
      "left": "criticism leads to feelings of guilt",
      "right": "criticism leads to feelings of anger",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0,
        "E": 0.16,
        "S": 0.08,
        "N": 0,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.56,
        "J": 0.09,
        "P": 0
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: when judging others, considers intent or only considers outcome?",
      "left": "when judging others, considers intent",
      "right": "only considers outcome",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0,
        "E": 0.02,
        "S": 0.25,
        "N": 0,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.64,
        "J": 0.07,
        "P": 0
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 13,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: uses reason or uses instinct?",
      "left": "uses reason",
      "right": "uses instinct",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0,
        "E": 0.37,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.33,
        "F": 1.17,
        "T": 0,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.45
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 15,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: trusts personal experience or trusts theory?",
      "left": "trusts personal experience",
      "right": "trusts theory",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0.26,
        "E": 0,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.37,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.67,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.04
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 20,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: thinks role models are important or thinks the importance of role models is exaggerated?",
      "left": "thinks role models are important",
      "right": "thinks the importance of role models is exaggerated",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0.45,
        "E": 0,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.02,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.62,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.2
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 22,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: afraid of the dark or likes the dark?",
      "left": "afraid of the dark",
      "right": "likes the dark",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0.26,
        "E": 0,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.27,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.54,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.01
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 26,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: humble or can be a bit arrogant?",
      "left": "humble",
      "right": "can be a bit arrogant",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0,
        "E": 0.37,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.24,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.68,
        "J": 0.01,
        "P": 0
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 28,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: can be a bit arrogant or humble?",
      "left": "can be a bit arrogant",
      "right": "humble",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0.32,
        "E": 0,
        "S": 0.17,
        "N": 0,
        "F": 0.63,
        "T": 0,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.06
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 29,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: wants people's respect or wants their love?",
      "left": "wants people's respect",
      "right": "wants their love",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0,
        "E": 0.22,
        "S": 0.37,
        "N": 0,
        "F": 1.18,
        "T": 0,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.4
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 40,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: cares if something is good or bad or cares if something is true or false?",
      "left": "cares if something is good or bad",
      "right": "cares if something is true or false",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0.19,
        "E": 0,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.14,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 1.12,
        "J": 0.12,
        "P": 0
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 43,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: likes nature or likes human industry?",
      "left": "likes nature",
      "right": "likes human industry",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0,
        "E": 0.17,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.52,
        "J": 0.03,
        "P": 0
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 48,
      "prompt": "Deep down, are you more sentimental or grim?",
      "left": "sentimental",
      "right": "grim",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0.4,
        "E": 0,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.28,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 1.07,
        "J": 0.13,
        "P": 0
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 52,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: if a lawyer, would prefer to be a prosecutor or would prefer to be defense attorney?",
      "left": "if a lawyer, would prefer to be a prosecutor",
      "right": "would prefer to be defense attorney",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0.11,
        "E": 0,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.15,
        "F": 0.65,
        "T": 0,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.28
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 55,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: likes to eavesdrop or finds other people's conversations too boring?",
      "left": "likes to eavesdrop",
      "right": "finds other people's conversations too boring",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0.21,
        "E": 0,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.2,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.55,
        "J": 0.14,
        "P": 0
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 57,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: sceptical or wants to believe?",
      "left": "sceptical",
      "right": "wants to believe",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0,
        "E": 0.46,
        "S": 0.18,
        "N": 0,
        "F": 1.17,
        "T": 0,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.18
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 70,
      "prompt": "Deep down, are you more sincere or sarcastic?",
      "left": "sincere",
      "right": "sarcastic",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0.06,
        "E": 0,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.03,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.87,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.04
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 72,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: appreciates the scenery around them or too distracted to take a look?",
      "left": "appreciates the scenery around them",
      "right": "too distracted to take a look",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0.09,
        "E": 0,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.14,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.42,
        "J": 0.04,
        "P": 0
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 73,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: worries most about tripping and falling in the dark or imagines monsters in the dark?",
      "left": "worries most about tripping and falling in the dark",
      "right": "imagines monsters in the dark",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0.02,
        "E": 0,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.36,
        "F": 0.49,
        "T": 0,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.28
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 75,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: seeks clarity or seeks harmony?",
      "left": "seeks clarity",
      "right": "seeks harmony",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0,
        "E": 0.16,
        "S": 0.17,
        "N": 0,
        "F": 1.05,
        "T": 0,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.34
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 86,
      "prompt": "Deep down, are you more literal or poetic?",
      "left": "literal",
      "right": "poetic",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0.05,
        "E": 0,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.64,
        "F": 1.02,
        "T": 0,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.44
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 90,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: looks on the bright side or finds faults?",
      "left": "looks on the bright side",
      "right": "finds faults",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0.64,
        "E": 0,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.08,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.7,
        "J": 0.41,
        "P": 0
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 91,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: thinks it is better to be naive or thinks it is better to be paranoid?",
      "left": "thinks it is better to be naive",
      "right": "thinks it is better to be paranoid",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0.38,
        "E": 0,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.11,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.56,
        "J": 0.24,
        "P": 0
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 92,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: worries about getting scammed all the time or too trusting?",
      "left": "worries about getting scammed all the time",
      "right": "too trusting",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0,
        "E": 0.37,
        "S": 0.15,
        "N": 0,
        "F": 0.58,
        "T": 0,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.15
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 93,
      "prompt": "In everyday life, are you more jealous or greedy?",
      "left": "jealous",
      "right": "greedy",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0,
        "E": 0.14,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.38,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.04
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 94,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: worried about the dangers of technology or thinks technology is always good?",
      "left": "worried about the dangers of technology",
      "right": "thinks technology is always good",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0,
        "E": 0.05,
        "S": 0.15,
        "N": 0,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.4,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.15
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 96,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: wants to believe or sceptical?",
      "left": "wants to believe",
      "right": "sceptical",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0.39,
        "E": 0,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.17,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 1.1,
        "J": 0.16,
        "P": 0
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 100,
      "prompt": "Day to day, are you more idealistic or cynical?",
      "left": "idealistic",
      "right": "cynical",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0.45,
        "E": 0,
        "S": 0.27,
        "N": 0,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.83,
        "J": 0.35,
        "P": 0
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 101,
      "prompt": "Are you more artistic or scientific?",
      "left": "artistic",
      "right": "scientific",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0.21,
        "E": 0,
        "S": 0.13,
        "N": 0,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 1.08,
        "J": 0.42,
        "P": 0
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 103,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: finds natural disasters exciting or finds natural disasters tragic?",
      "left": "finds natural disasters exciting",
      "right": "finds natural disasters tragic",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0,
        "E": 0.05,
        "S": 0.29,
        "N": 0,
        "F": 0.66,
        "T": 0,
        "J": 0.2,
        "P": 0
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 109,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: wants to know what others think or decides on their own?",
      "left": "wants to know what others think",
      "right": "decides on their own",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0.19,
        "E": 0,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.46,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.78,
        "J": 0.02,
        "P": 0
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 113,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: sounds and smells often bring back childhood memories or childhood memories never come unintentionally?",
      "left": "sounds and smells often bring back childhood memories",
      "right": "childhood memories never come unintentionally",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0.14,
        "E": 0,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.11,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.54,
        "J": 0.13,
        "P": 0
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 115,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: likes words or likes numbers?",
      "left": "likes words",
      "right": "likes numbers",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0.1,
        "E": 0,
        "S": 0.28,
        "N": 0,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.7,
        "J": 0.22,
        "P": 0
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 116,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: argues for ideas or argues against ideas?",
      "left": "argues for ideas",
      "right": "argues against ideas",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0.04,
        "E": 0,
        "S": 0.2,
        "N": 0,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.36,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.07
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 121,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: if a lawyer, would prefer to be a defense attorney or would prefer to be prosecutor?",
      "left": "if a lawyer, would prefer to be a defense attorney",
      "right": "would prefer to be prosecutor",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0,
        "E": 0.13,
        "S": 0.19,
        "N": 0,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.55,
        "J": 0.25,
        "P": 0
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 122,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: gives hints or tell it straight up?",
      "left": "gives hints",
      "right": "tell it straight up",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0,
        "E": 0.35,
        "S": 0.09,
        "N": 0,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.75,
        "J": 0.11,
        "P": 0
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 125,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: judges music based on melody or judges music based on lyrics?",
      "left": "judges music based on melody",
      "right": "judges music based on lyrics",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0.01,
        "E": 0,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0,
        "F": 0.09,
        "T": 0,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.03
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 129,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: keeps pets or has no interest in pets?",
      "left": "keeps pets",
      "right": "has no interest in pets",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0.15,
        "E": 0,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.15,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.4,
        "J": 0.13,
        "P": 0
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 130,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: easy to gross out or fascinated by disgusting things?",
      "left": "easy to gross out",
      "right": "fascinated by disgusting things",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0.09,
        "E": 0,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.25,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.38,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.12
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 133,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: shares deepest secrets or has no secrets worth sharing?",
      "left": "shares deepest secrets",
      "right": "has no secrets worth sharing",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0.58,
        "E": 0,
        "S": 0.11,
        "N": 0,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.69,
        "J": 0.19,
        "P": 0
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 140,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: interested in family history or wants to leave that all behind?",
      "left": "interested in family history",
      "right": "wants to leave that all behind",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0.07,
        "E": 0,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.11,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.29,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.21
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 141,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: how it is done matters or only the end results matters?",
      "left": "how it is done matters",
      "right": "only the end results matters",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0,
        "E": 0.04,
        "S": 0.11,
        "N": 0,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.45,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.12
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 155,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: tries to give convincing speeches or tries to give inspiring speeches?",
      "left": "tries to give convincing speeches",
      "right": "tries to give inspiring speeches",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0,
        "E": 0.39,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.28,
        "F": 1.04,
        "T": 0,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.33
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 158,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: likes getting gifts or has no need for gifts?",
      "left": "likes getting gifts",
      "right": "has no need for gifts",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0.3,
        "E": 0,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.23,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.58,
        "J": 0.22,
        "P": 0
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 163,
      "prompt": "Are you more impatient or tolerant?",
      "left": "impatient",
      "right": "tolerant",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0.19,
        "E": 0,
        "S": 0.12,
        "N": 0,
        "F": 0.4,
        "T": 0,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.12
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 164,
      "prompt": "Deep down, are you more jittery or smooth?",
      "left": "jittery",
      "right": "smooth",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0,
        "E": 0.23,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.07,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.27,
        "J": 0.19,
        "P": 0
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 169,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: people are basically good or people are basically evil?",
      "left": "people are basically good",
      "right": "people are basically evil",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0.34,
        "E": 0,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.03,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.65,
        "J": 0.17,
        "P": 0
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 171,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: thinks people can change or thinks people will only stay the same?",
      "left": "thinks people can change",
      "right": "thinks people will only stay the same",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0.24,
        "E": 0,
        "S": 0.06,
        "N": 0,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.59,
        "J": 0.34,
        "P": 0
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 173,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: tries to behave intelligently or tries to show their creativity?",
      "left": "tries to behave intelligently",
      "right": "tries to show their creativity",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0,
        "E": 0.27,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.14,
        "F": 0.9,
        "T": 0,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.52
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 177,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: aware of surroundings or easy to sneak up on?",
      "left": "aware of surroundings",
      "right": "easy to sneak up on",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0,
        "E": 0.02,
        "S": 0.01,
        "N": 0,
        "F": 0.32,
        "T": 0,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.29
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 180,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: tries to give inspiring speeches or tries to give convincing speeches?",
      "left": "tries to give inspiring speeches",
      "right": "tries to give convincing speeches",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0.38,
        "E": 0,
        "S": 0.18,
        "N": 0,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.99,
        "J": 0.17,
        "P": 0
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 181,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: identifies with characters in stories or never really seems to like any fictional characters?",
      "left": "identifies with characters in stories",
      "right": "never really seems to like any fictional characters",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0,
        "E": 0.06,
        "S": 0.28,
        "N": 0,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.49,
        "J": 0.12,
        "P": 0
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 182,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: wants to be tough or wants to be classy?",
      "left": "wants to be tough",
      "right": "wants to be classy",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0,
        "E": 0.13,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.06,
        "F": 0.25,
        "T": 0,
        "J": 0.04,
        "P": 0
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 186,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: has meaningful dreams or has dreams that make no sense, about things that do not matter?",
      "left": "has meaningful dreams",
      "right": "has dreams that make no sense, about things that do not matter",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0.03,
        "E": 0,
        "S": 0.14,
        "N": 0,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.29,
        "J": 0.04,
        "P": 0
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 189,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: wants honest friends or wants impressive friends?",
      "left": "wants honest friends",
      "right": "wants impressive friends",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0,
        "E": 0.2,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.04,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.23,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.04
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 194,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: values emotions or uncomfortable with emotions?",
      "left": "values emotions",
      "right": "uncomfortable with emotions",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0.55,
        "E": 0,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.03,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 1.67,
        "J": 0.22,
        "P": 0
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 196,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: worries about who they are or accepts who they are?",
      "left": "worries about who they are",
      "right": "accepts who they are",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0,
        "E": 0.33,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.09,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.44,
        "J": 0.04,
        "P": 0
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 203,
      "prompt": "Day to day, are you more trendy or hardcore?",
      "left": "trendy",
      "right": "hardcore",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0.12,
        "E": 0,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.07,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.29,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.02
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 206,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: thinks some people are all bad or knows everyone has a little bit of good in them?",
      "left": "thinks some people are all bad",
      "right": "knows everyone has a little bit of good in them",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0,
        "E": 0.43,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.11,
        "F": 0.78,
        "T": 0,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.23
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 207,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: likes certain types of music or likes all types?",
      "left": "likes certain types of music",
      "right": "likes all types",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0,
        "E": 0.29,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.03,
        "F": 0.37,
        "T": 0,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.16
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 208,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: worries about getting let down or worries about letting other people down?",
      "left": "worries about getting let down",
      "right": "worries about letting other people down",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0,
        "E": 0.09,
        "S": 0.1,
        "N": 0,
        "F": 0.42,
        "T": 0,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.1
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 213,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: often mistaken as being angry or anger often goes unnoticed by others?",
      "left": "often mistaken as being angry",
      "right": "anger often goes unnoticed by others",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0,
        "E": 0.09,
        "S": 0.07,
        "N": 0,
        "F": 0.4,
        "T": 0,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.21
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 214,
      "prompt": "Deep down, are you more cooperative or competitive?",
      "left": "cooperative",
      "right": "competitive",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0,
        "E": 0.28,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.13,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.64,
        "J": 0.1,
        "P": 0
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 215,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: fears death or accepts death?",
      "left": "fears death",
      "right": "accepts death",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0.03,
        "E": 0,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.27,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.29,
        "J": 0.1,
        "P": 0
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 228,
      "prompt": "Day to day, are you more passionate or jaded?",
      "left": "passionate",
      "right": "jaded",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0.56,
        "E": 0,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.02,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.73,
        "J": 0.21,
        "P": 0
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 230,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: easily hurt or thick-skinned?",
      "left": "easily hurt",
      "right": "thick-skinned",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0,
        "E": 0.22,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.08,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 1.1,
        "J": 0.08,
        "P": 0
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 231,
      "prompt": "Are you more arrogant or insecure?",
      "left": "arrogant",
      "right": "insecure",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0.54,
        "E": 0,
        "S": 0.1,
        "N": 0,
        "F": 0.67,
        "T": 0,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.19
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 237,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: gets bored of songs quickly or never gets tired of a good song?",
      "left": "gets bored of songs quickly",
      "right": "never gets tired of a good song",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0.15,
        "E": 0,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0,
        "F": 0.18,
        "T": 0,
        "J": 0.09,
        "P": 0
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 239,
      "prompt": "In everyday life, are you more practical or dreamy?",
      "left": "practical",
      "right": "dreamy",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0.01,
        "E": 0,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.7,
        "F": 0.88,
        "T": 0,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.76
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 244,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: gives complements or receives compliments?",
      "left": "gives complements",
      "right": "receives compliments",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0.13,
        "E": 0,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.74,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.02
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 246,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: thinks about what they would do as a criminal or does not like the idea of crime?",
      "left": "thinks about what they would do as a criminal",
      "right": "does not like the idea of crime",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0.03,
        "E": 0,
        "S": 0.47,
        "N": 0,
        "F": 0.51,
        "T": 0,
        "J": 0.34,
        "P": 0
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 252,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: bothered by disgusting things or fails to notice how gross things are?",
      "left": "bothered by disgusting things",
      "right": "fails to notice how gross things are",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0,
        "E": 0.11,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.23,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.42,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.34
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 254,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: prefer to read the news or prefer to read a story?",
      "left": "prefer to read the news",
      "right": "prefer to read a story",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0.19,
        "E": 0,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.01,
        "F": 0.43,
        "T": 0,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.24
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 259,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: wants to be good at fixing things or wants to be good at fixing people?",
      "left": "wants to be good at fixing things",
      "right": "wants to be good at fixing people",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0,
        "E": 0.4,
        "S": 0.04,
        "N": 0,
        "F": 1.28,
        "T": 0,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.1
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 265,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: likes looking at pictures of them as a baby or hates that?",
      "left": "likes looking at pictures of them as a baby",
      "right": "hates that",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0.52,
        "E": 0,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.14,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.86,
        "J": 0.1,
        "P": 0
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 275,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: thinks \\\"robotic\\\" is an insult or strives to have a mechanical mind?",
      "left": "thinks \\\"robotic\\\" is an insult",
      "right": "strives to have a mechanical mind",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0.45,
        "E": 0,
        "S": 0.02,
        "N": 0,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 1.21,
        "J": 0.41,
        "P": 0
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 281,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: buys things they like or only buys things they really need?",
      "left": "buys things they like",
      "right": "only buys things they really need",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0.32,
        "E": 0,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.15,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.39,
        "J": 0.35,
        "P": 0
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 283,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: trusts personal experience or trusts theoretical knowledge?",
      "left": "trusts personal experience",
      "right": "trusts theoretical knowledge",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0.3,
        "E": 0,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.45,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.68,
        "J": 0.09,
        "P": 0
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 285,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: follows the heart or follows the head?",
      "left": "follows the heart",
      "right": "follows the head",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0.36,
        "E": 0,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.01,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 1.6,
        "J": 0.45,
        "P": 0
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 291,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: tactful with others or blunt with others?",
      "left": "tactful with others",
      "right": "blunt with others",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0,
        "E": 0.02,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.04,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.86,
        "J": 0.07,
        "P": 0
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 292,
      "prompt": "Deep down, are you more nervous or calm?",
      "left": "nervous",
      "right": "calm",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0,
        "E": 0.28,
        "S": 0.05,
        "N": 0,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.56,
        "J": 0.03,
        "P": 0
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 295,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: bases morality on compassion or bases morality on justice?",
      "left": "bases morality on compassion",
      "right": "bases morality on justice",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0.16,
        "E": 0,
        "S": 0.02,
        "N": 0,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 1.32,
        "J": 0.39,
        "P": 0
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 297,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: judges a painting on how realistic it is or judges a painting on the feeling it conveys?",
      "left": "judges a painting on how realistic it is",
      "right": "judges a painting on the feeling it conveys",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0,
        "E": 0.07,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.34,
        "F": 0.84,
        "T": 0,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.33
      }
    }
  ],
  "JP": [
    {
      "id": 4,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: loses track of time or good sense of time?",
      "left": "loses track of time",
      "right": "good sense of time",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0,
        "E": 0.19,
        "S": 0.4,
        "N": 0,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.32,
        "J": 0.83,
        "P": 0
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: wishes their life was more interesting or finds their life interesting enough?",
      "left": "wishes their life was more interesting",
      "right": "finds their life interesting enough",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0,
        "E": 0.18,
        "S": 0.14,
        "N": 0,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.13,
        "J": 0.25,
        "P": 0
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: makes things or breaks things?",
      "left": "makes things",
      "right": "breaks things",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0,
        "E": 0.19,
        "S": 0.12,
        "N": 0,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.02,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.36
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 10,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: likes knowing all the facts or likes filling in the blanks?",
      "left": "likes knowing all the facts",
      "right": "likes filling in the blanks",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0,
        "E": 0.13,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.52,
        "F": 0.38,
        "T": 0,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.58
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 16,
      "prompt": "When people describe you, are you more prepares or improvises?",
      "left": "prepares",
      "right": "improvises",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0,
        "E": 0.43,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.28,
        "F": 0.15,
        "T": 0,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 1.43
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 19,
      "prompt": "Day to day, are you more organized or chaotic?",
      "left": "organized",
      "right": "chaotic",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0,
        "E": 0.16,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.21,
        "F": 0.25,
        "T": 0,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 1.15
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 31,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: commits or keeps options open?",
      "left": "commits",
      "right": "keeps options open",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0,
        "E": 0.04,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.25,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.14,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.87
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 35,
      "prompt": "In everyday life, are you more tricky or steady?",
      "left": "tricky",
      "right": "steady",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0.2,
        "E": 0,
        "S": 0.26,
        "N": 0,
        "F": 0.05,
        "T": 0,
        "J": 0.52,
        "P": 0
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 36,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: assured by routine or bored by routine?",
      "left": "assured by routine",
      "right": "bored by routine",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0,
        "E": 0.6,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.59,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.82
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 37,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: needs certainty or needs flexibility?",
      "left": "needs certainty",
      "right": "needs flexibility",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0,
        "E": 0.44,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.39,
        "F": 0.16,
        "T": 0,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.82
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 38,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: gets work done right away or procrastinates?",
      "left": "gets work done right away",
      "right": "procrastinates",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0.1,
        "E": 0,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.11,
        "F": 0.29,
        "T": 0,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.93
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 41,
      "prompt": "When people describe you, are you more methodical or astonishing?",
      "left": "methodical",
      "right": "astonishing",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0,
        "E": 0.45,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.21,
        "F": 0.51,
        "T": 0,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.72
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 51,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: double checks their work or hopes for the best?",
      "left": "double checks their work",
      "right": "hopes for the best",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0,
        "E": 0.44,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.07,
        "F": 0.35,
        "T": 0,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.82
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 56,
      "prompt": "In everyday life, are you more decides or guesses?",
      "left": "decides",
      "right": "guesses",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0.02,
        "E": 0,
        "S": 0.04,
        "N": 0,
        "F": 0.56,
        "T": 0,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.94
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 58,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: has been through a lot of tough times or has had an easy life?",
      "left": "has been through a lot of tough times",
      "right": "has had an easy life",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0,
        "E": 0.17,
        "S": 0.21,
        "N": 0,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.19,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.3
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 60,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: answers mail right away or gets behind on answering mail?",
      "left": "answers mail right away",
      "right": "gets behind on answering mail",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0.16,
        "E": 0,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.2,
        "F": 0.12,
        "T": 0,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.7
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 65,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: always finishes sentences or can trail off in the middle of a sentences?",
      "left": "always finishes sentences",
      "right": "can trail off in the middle of a sentences",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0.19,
        "E": 0,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.16,
        "F": 0.47,
        "T": 0,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.63
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 71,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: always has a backup plan or never needs a backup plan?",
      "left": "always has a backup plan",
      "right": "never needs a backup plan",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0,
        "E": 0.21,
        "S": 0.03,
        "N": 0,
        "F": 0.16,
        "T": 0,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.6
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 85,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: makes rules or breaks rules?",
      "left": "makes rules",
      "right": "breaks rules",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0,
        "E": 0.44,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.45,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.06,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.86
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 87,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: needs to work or only works because they must?",
      "left": "needs to work",
      "right": "only works because they must",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0.07,
        "E": 0,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.06,
        "F": 0.23,
        "T": 0,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.78
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 99,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: sticks to the plan or adapts the plan on the fly?",
      "left": "sticks to the plan",
      "right": "adapts the plan on the fly",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0,
        "E": 0.49,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.4,
        "F": 0.12,
        "T": 0,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 1.07
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 106,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: everyone breaks the law now and then or only bad people break the law?",
      "left": "everyone breaks the law now and then",
      "right": "only bad people break the law",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0.15,
        "E": 0,
        "S": 0.4,
        "N": 0,
        "F": 0.18,
        "T": 0,
        "J": 0.51,
        "P": 0
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 124,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: thinks only the lucky succeed or knows only the hard-working get lucky?",
      "left": "thinks only the lucky succeed",
      "right": "knows only the hard-working get lucky",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0,
        "E": 0.02,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.06,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.26,
        "J": 0.31,
        "P": 0
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 128,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: views things as many shades of grey or views things as black and white?",
      "left": "views things as many shades of grey",
      "right": "views things as black and white",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0,
        "E": 0.14,
        "S": 0.29,
        "N": 0,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.25,
        "J": 0.39,
        "P": 0
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 131,
      "prompt": "Deep down, are you more fumbling or graceful?",
      "left": "fumbling",
      "right": "graceful",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0,
        "E": 0.24,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.03,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.1,
        "J": 0.28,
        "P": 0
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 134,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: light sleeper or deep sleeper?",
      "left": "light sleeper",
      "right": "deep sleeper",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0,
        "E": 0.08,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.03,
        "F": 0.03,
        "T": 0,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.14
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 137,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: get a task done in one go or does a task a little at a time?",
      "left": "get a task done in one go",
      "right": "does a task a little at a time",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0.23,
        "E": 0,
        "S": 0.01,
        "N": 0,
        "F": 0.31,
        "T": 0,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.41
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 143,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: plans far ahead or plans at the last minute?",
      "left": "plans far ahead",
      "right": "plans at the last minute",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0,
        "E": 0.3,
        "S": 0.04,
        "N": 0,
        "F": 0.29,
        "T": 0,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 1.26
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 150,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: careful with money or a high roller?",
      "left": "careful with money",
      "right": "a high roller",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0,
        "E": 0.42,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.06,
        "F": 0.28,
        "T": 0,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.56
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 151,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: has an accurate internal clock or often has no idea what time it is?",
      "left": "has an accurate internal clock",
      "right": "often has no idea what time it is",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0.03,
        "E": 0,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.08,
        "F": 0.16,
        "T": 0,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.59
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 152,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: supports a strong government or supports strong personal freedoms?",
      "left": "supports a strong government",
      "right": "supports strong personal freedoms",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0.08,
        "E": 0,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.18,
        "F": 0.02,
        "T": 0,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.31
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 156,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: loyal to friends or loyal to family?",
      "left": "loyal to friends",
      "right": "loyal to family",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0.04,
        "E": 0,
        "S": 0.15,
        "N": 0,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.04,
        "J": 0.27,
        "P": 0
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 162,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: wishes they could read minds or wishes they could fly?",
      "left": "wishes they could read minds",
      "right": "wishes they could fly",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0,
        "E": 0.09,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.03,
        "F": 0.25,
        "T": 0,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.38
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 165,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: well dressed or scruffy?",
      "left": "well dressed",
      "right": "scruffy",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0.31,
        "E": 0,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.05,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.07,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.4
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 166,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: never wants to make a mistake or accepts mistakes as inevitable?",
      "left": "never wants to make a mistake",
      "right": "accepts mistakes as inevitable",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0,
        "E": 0.41,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.17,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.03,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.58
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 167,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: chooses carefully or chooses randomly?",
      "left": "chooses carefully",
      "right": "chooses randomly",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0,
        "E": 0.39,
        "S": 0.05,
        "N": 0,
        "F": 0.34,
        "T": 0,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.66
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 170,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: interests often change or has stable interests?",
      "left": "interests often change",
      "right": "has stable interests",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0.35,
        "E": 0,
        "S": 0.21,
        "N": 0,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.15,
        "J": 0.63,
        "P": 0
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 175,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: works hard or plays hard?",
      "left": "works hard",
      "right": "plays hard",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0,
        "E": 0.31,
        "S": 0.02,
        "N": 0,
        "F": 0.21,
        "T": 0,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.82
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 176,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: feels that time passes to slowly or feels that time passes to quickly?",
      "left": "feels that time passes to slowly",
      "right": "feels that time passes to quickly",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0,
        "E": 0.06,
        "S": 0.01,
        "N": 0,
        "F": 0.09,
        "T": 0,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.11
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 179,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: enjoys cracking joints or cracking joints is gross?",
      "left": "enjoys cracking joints",
      "right": "cracking joints is gross",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0.19,
        "E": 0,
        "S": 0.04,
        "N": 0,
        "F": 0.16,
        "T": 0,
        "J": 0.31,
        "P": 0
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 187,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: always looks for the best price or takes the first price?",
      "left": "always looks for the best price",
      "right": "takes the first price",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0,
        "E": 0.08,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.09,
        "F": 0.25,
        "T": 0,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.28
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 200,
      "prompt": "When people describe you, are you more ambitious or rebellious?",
      "left": "ambitious",
      "right": "rebellious",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0.09,
        "E": 0,
        "S": 0.01,
        "N": 0,
        "F": 0.14,
        "T": 0,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.66
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 212,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: stays up late or rises early?",
      "left": "stays up late",
      "right": "rises early",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0,
        "E": 0.06,
        "S": 0.14,
        "N": 0,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.15,
        "J": 0.48,
        "P": 0
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 217,
      "prompt": "When people describe you, are you more creative or wise?",
      "left": "creative",
      "right": "wise",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0.14,
        "E": 0,
        "S": 0.09,
        "N": 0,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.33,
        "J": 0.46,
        "P": 0
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 223,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: has neat handwriting or has messy handwriting?",
      "left": "has neat handwriting",
      "right": "has messy handwriting",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0.02,
        "E": 0,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.18,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.14,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.45
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 224,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: likes being on solid ground or dreams of the sea?",
      "left": "likes being on solid ground",
      "right": "dreams of the sea",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0,
        "E": 0.09,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.37,
        "F": 0.43,
        "T": 0,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.51
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 225,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: bothered by spelling mistakes or is fine with spelling mistakes, as long as the meaning comes through?",
      "left": "bothered by spelling mistakes",
      "right": "is fine with spelling mistakes, as long as the meaning comes through",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0,
        "E": 0.26,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.11,
        "F": 0.13,
        "T": 0,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.44
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 227,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: forever young or all grown up?",
      "left": "forever young",
      "right": "all grown up",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0.45,
        "E": 0,
        "S": 0.05,
        "N": 0,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.38,
        "J": 0.66,
        "P": 0
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 235,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: often misplaces their keys or has a system so that does not happen?",
      "left": "often misplaces their keys",
      "right": "has a system so that does not happen",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0.2,
        "E": 0,
        "S": 0.14,
        "N": 0,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.43,
        "J": 0.8,
        "P": 0
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 236,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: keeps a clean room or just puts stuff where ever?",
      "left": "keeps a clean room",
      "right": "just puts stuff where ever",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0,
        "E": 0.05,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.15,
        "F": 0.19,
        "T": 0,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.93
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 243,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: knows what they want or still trying to figure it all out?",
      "left": "knows what they want",
      "right": "still trying to figure it all out",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0.39,
        "E": 0,
        "S": 0.25,
        "N": 0,
        "F": 0.39,
        "T": 0,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.76
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 245,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: likes to \\\"just drive\\\" or would never drive without a purpose?",
      "left": "likes to \\\"just drive\\\"",
      "right": "would never drive without a purpose",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0.31,
        "E": 0,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.06,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.49,
        "J": 0.63,
        "P": 0
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 248,
      "prompt": "When people describe you, are you more scheduled or spontaneous?",
      "left": "scheduled",
      "right": "spontaneous",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0,
        "E": 0.57,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.34,
        "F": 0.35,
        "T": 0,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 1.17
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 249,
      "prompt": "Day to day, are you more steady or unstable?",
      "left": "steady",
      "right": "unstable",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0.19,
        "E": 0,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.16,
        "F": 0.34,
        "T": 0,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.56
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 251,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: rises early or sleeps late?",
      "left": "rises early",
      "right": "sleeps late",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0.1,
        "E": 0,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.08,
        "F": 0.1,
        "T": 0,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.58
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 260,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: works in fits and bursts or works through it steadily?",
      "left": "works in fits and bursts",
      "right": "works through it steadily",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0.23,
        "E": 0,
        "S": 0.38,
        "N": 0,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.3,
        "J": 0.84,
        "P": 0
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 267,
      "prompt": "In everyday life, are you more reckless or solid?",
      "left": "reckless",
      "right": "solid",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0.4,
        "E": 0,
        "S": 0.1,
        "N": 0,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.21,
        "J": 0.87,
        "P": 0
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 271,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: does a good job handling the preparation or does a good job handling the fallout?",
      "left": "does a good job handling the preparation",
      "right": "does a good job handling the fallout",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0,
        "E": 0.3,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.17,
        "F": 0.05,
        "T": 0,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.72
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 272,
      "prompt": "Day to day, are you more mysterious or reliable?",
      "left": "mysterious",
      "right": "reliable",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0,
        "E": 0.3,
        "S": 0.41,
        "N": 0,
        "F": 0.06,
        "T": 0,
        "J": 0.53,
        "P": 0
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 274,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: follows rules or breaks rules?",
      "left": "follows rules",
      "right": "breaks rules",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0,
        "E": 0.37,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.56,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.24,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.66
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 277,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: puts time into choosing/preparing food or goes for whatever is simplest?",
      "left": "puts time into choosing/preparing food",
      "right": "goes for whatever is simplest",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0.1,
        "E": 0,
        "S": 0.27,
        "N": 0,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.17,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.45
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 280,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: does their best or does what they need to get by?",
      "left": "does their best",
      "right": "does what they need to get by",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0.15,
        "E": 0,
        "S": 0.13,
        "N": 0,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.17,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.72
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 286,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: demands precision or satisfied with good enough?",
      "left": "demands precision",
      "right": "satisfied with good enough",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0,
        "E": 0.25,
        "S": 0.12,
        "N": 0,
        "F": 0.5,
        "T": 0,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.68
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 287,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: makes lists or relies on memory?",
      "left": "makes lists",
      "right": "relies on memory",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0,
        "E": 0.06,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.14,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.13,
        "J": 0,
        "P": 0.75
      }
    },
    {
      "id": 289,
      "prompt": "Which feels more like you: never edits their writing once they are done or always goes back and makes many revisions?",
      "left": "never edits their writing once they are done",
      "right": "always goes back and makes many revisions",
      "weights": {
        "I": 0.16,
        "E": 0,
        "S": 0,
        "N": 0.06,
        "F": 0,
        "T": 0.02,
        "J": 0.41,
        "P": 0
      }
    }
  ]
}
